export default [
    {
        id:1,
        question: "How many clubs have won the Euroleague title?",
        answer1:"22",
        answer2:"14",
        answer3:"28",
        answer4: "18",
        correct:1
    },
    {
        id:2,
        question: "Which team has the most EuroLeague titles?",
        answer1:"CSKA Moscow",
        answer2:"Real Madrid",
        answer3:"Maccabi Tel Aviv",
        answer4: "Panathinaikos Athens",
        correct:2
    },
    {
        id:3,
        question: "How many times has Virtus Bologna reached the final?",
        answer1:"5",
        answer2:"3",
        answer3:"0",
        answer4: "6",
        correct:1
    },
    {
        id:4,
        question: "How many times has Varese reached the final?",
        answer1:"6",
        answer2:"7",
        answer3:"8",
        answer4: "10",
        correct:4
    },
    {
        id:5,
        question: "Who was played the most matches in euroleague history?",
        answer1:"Kyle Hines",
        answer2:"Sergio Llull",
        answer3:"Georgios Printezis",
        answer4: "Juan Carlos Navarro",
        correct:1
    },
    {
        id:6,
        question: "Who has scored the most points in Euroleague history?",
        answer1:"Nando de Colo",
        answer2:"Vassilis Spanoulis",
        answer3:"Mike James",
        answer4: "Juan Carlos Navarro",
        correct:3
    },
    {
        id:7,
        question: "Who was the euroleague champion in 2022",
        answer1:"Real Madrid",
        answer2:"Anadolu Efes",
        answer3:"Virtus Bologna",
        answer4: "Olympiacos Piraeus",
        correct:2
    },
    {
        id:8,
        question: "When was the last time Maccabi Tel Aviv won the Euroleague?",
        answer1:"2014",
        answer2:"2020",
        answer3:"2005",
        answer4: "2008",
        correct:1
    },
    {
        id:9,
        question: "How many final 4 mvps does Vassilis Spanoulis have?",
        answer1:"3",
        answer2:"4",
        answer3:"1",
        answer4: "2",
        correct:1
    },
    {
        id:10,
        question: "Who was the euroleague champion in 2023",
        answer1:"Olympiacos Piraeus",
        answer2:"AS Monaco",
        answer3:"Barcelona",
        answer4: "Real Madrid",
        correct:4
    },
]